

PROFILE

I am a senior full stack software engineer and have over 8 years of experience in web and Mobile app design and development.

I have mastered JavaScript and its frameworks like as React/Next, Vue/Nuxt, TypeScript, Node, express and have good eyes in modern website design.

Fast communication + best quality

CONTACT

Skype: live:.cid.8f2733b90552eb3b

EMAIL:

<u>Goldenstarlight1016@gmail.com</u> Phone:

+15185941940

HOBBIES

Badminton Ping-Pong reading

JAY JAMES

Full stack Software Engineer

EDUCATION

Nanyang Technical University

9/2010 - 10/2013

- -Specialized in Computer science
- -Major: Computer programming
- -Degree: Master's degree

WORK EXPERIENCE

IBM (Front end application developer)

2/2015-7/2017

- -Worked for IBM for 3 years
- -Build web application using React.js and integrated several APIs
- -role: designer, developer, manager
- -salary: \$6000/month

Ambitious people group (JavaScript developer)

9/2018-4/2021

- -worked for 4 years
- -several kinds of software development Tracking solution, Cloud/IoT based Projects
- -JavaScript, React, TypeScript, AWS, IoT,
- -salary: \$4500 /month

Upwork (Full stack Software Engineer)

7/2021-4/2022

- -Worked as a full stack software engineer for Upwork
- -Main Stack is Front end design and development & API design, dev
- -bitcoin, smart contract, Ethereum, solidity
- -\$35/hr

MAIN SKILLS

